Visit turkision.com for more!
Come on. We are just starting.
Come on, jackals!
I am still alive!
Alps! Everyone to horses!
Cukurdibi.
It happened at Cukurdibi.
Osman. My Allah, protect him.
-Come on.
-Come on!
Yakup Bey.
Come on.
Boran!
We will go this way.
-There alps coming from the tribe.
-Come on Yakup Bey, there is no time.
You answer goodness with illness!
Where do you think you are running to?
Their arrogance made them blind! We
will make them right with our swords!
Attack, alps!
Don’t you know those who lay eyes
upon my land dies!
Ambush!
Be cautious!
Whoever did this knew we were coming!
You don't know who you are messing with!
The Righteous!
Come on alps! My father waits us!
-Konur!
-Yakup Bey!
Stop!
Konur is with us.
Come on, let us leave before alps arrive.
Osman.
So you are still alive.
I will take your life myself.
Why?
Why are you
still standing? This is th,e time, come on!
Ibrahim Bey! Melike Hatun!
This is not the time.
The reinforcements from the tribe should
be on its way.
Come on.
Ibrahim Bey!
I said, come on.
Boran!
Boran.
Konur!
Boran!
What are you up to!
Forgive me, my Bey.
We didn't foresee this happening.
Forgive us.
My Bey!
Osman!
My Bey.
-Are you alright?
-I am alright.
They ran off.
-Osman, are you alright?
-I am alright.
Even the devil would envy what they’ve done.
They placed the fires night before.
We couldn't have known.
They betrayed us, my Bey. To hell with their lives.
We couldn't have known Boran would do this.
A traitor wouldn't lock the door now would he?
What about Konur?
Did he have something to do with this?
Konur went after them as well.
We will learn their intentions.
However, what they've done here was the last straw.
-What will we do now, my Bey?
-We will not let them get away with this.
Of course we will make them pay.
Of course we will. Come on, let us move.
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
Thank Allah, you came back well, father.
Did you send word to Beys, Mehmed?
All the Beys have answered our call for war.
They will be here soon.
Good.
There are a lot of men to be teached at frontiers.
And how will we teach them, father?
With those?
Mehmed.
This is not the time to be seperated.
But to be united.
They released us from the captivity of Osman.
Do not forget that.
Ulcay and Tugay will watch them closely.
Their heads will roll with a single mistake.
Let the judge come..
..and justice be secured first.
Their fate will be dealt with later.
Mehmed. Are there any news from Alaeddin?
All villages and caves were
checked at southern and northern region.
However, they are still missing.
Now it is time for houses and caves..
..at the Dimbos region.
I will go there.
Tell Ulcay.
Let him come with you.
Search thoroughly together.
Ruknettin, the judge...
...is a great scholar.
I've heard his fame numerous times.
However, it is a pity I
will see his face in dark days like these.
It is.
We haven't seen him as well.
A great judge is coming..
..and we still can not find Alaeddin.
Come on, Mehmed.
Dogan, tell Ulcay.
Dogan, tell that
jackal, we will search from both sides.
Even his scent makes me nauseous.
Yakup Bey.
This search..
..is finding a needle in a hay bale.
There are many gutters at frontiers.
We need information from Osman.
Konur! Boran
Come on.
Yes, Ibrahim Bey.
You know everything about Osman.
Find where..
..Alaeddin is.
We are watching Osman and his tribe
for two days as per UIcay's request.
We know their every move.
We will give you
the right information to find Alaeddin.
Thank you.
I suppose there is
no harm searching for him from four sides.
Come now. Tell us.
Be well, my Bey.
-Thank Allah.
-Are you alright, my Bey?
-My Bey, are you alright?
-Thank Allah, we are alright. Do not worry.
-Thank Allah, we are alright.
-May you live long, my Bey.
May Allah protect you, my Bey.
What is it?
What is this?
Listen.
How could you have known?
Don't get your heads down.
Don't. Do not.
How could you have known that they'd
bury their children and attempt to run off?
How could you have
known that they'd set fires and traps?
This seems to be a game of Ulcay's.
What makes you think so, Osman Bey?
It may Ibrahim and Yakup too.
No.
I never believe our people can be this vile.
They want to make brothers fight each other.
Our people would never go this far.
If we do what they want,
..too much blood will be shed.
Too many heads will fall.
But we will prevent this...
...as much as we can and our morals allow us.
Didn't they violate the morals long ago, Osman Bey?
Losing a child, Gunduz Bey...
We all know what it does to a person...
...and what it can make people do.
Losing a child...
It's such poison that...
...it may be a great trouble...
...if it flows in the wrong vein.
But we..
...will never let this trouble rise.
Come on. I expect to see everyone in my tent.
Even if one of Kayis is excluded from the tribe
...they never lose contact.
They always keep in touch.
Thanks to this,
we know all the secret ways they use.
Ha, Boran?
For sure, we know them all.
If there aren't some they keep secret from us.
Well..
Yakup Bey must see your usefulness...
...so he can stop doubting.
Whatever is needed
will be done without hesitation, my Bey.
Now..
Let's see who can save Osman from us, Yakup Bey.
It's been obvious Osman will be destroyed...
..due to what he has done so far.
His end was just waiting for a reason.
He caused our children to die.
Only death is waiting for Osman now.
Whoever killed Ahmed
...they would never let the judge...
...secure the justice in these lands.
Justice is the
last thing they'd desire in these lands.
Yes. Yes.
Well... Judge is coming from Karesi.
And he's going to spend the night in the inn.
-Orhan.
-My Bey.
Elcim.
You go visit the judge.
And make him reach this land safely.
You should be
disguised. Don't let anyone notice you.
-As you order, my Bey.
Go now.
Well..
Alaaddin...
Send Hasan to Alaaddin.
We can't let anyone see him until the trial.
As you order, my Bey.
Gunduz Bey.
Let's talk about the conquest of Mekece.
In such time?
-Well...
No times can keep us away from the conquests.
We'd perform
the conquest even if we're deep in blood.
Now... Ibrahim Bey and Yakup Bey...
...are bringing
their armies not only for our lands...
...but also for the conquest of Mekece.
We need to act quickly.
For this reason, start
sending your alps for the conquest already.
Whatever you wish, Osman Bey.
Where are you?
Jackal!
Are you in your nest?
Melike Sultan...
You invited me.
So I got out of my nest and came here.
Make your wish now.
Kill Judge Rukneddin.
Our servant Kamil will take his place.
I've sent him a message.
He's going to hit the road soon.
Why would you want to kill the judge?
We know Alaaddin killed my son.
But the judge is going to demand witnesses...
...and investigate elaborately.
And this will make it longer.
Osman will try
to distract the judge in the meantime.
You're not leaving it to chance, huh?
Fine.
What will you do when
Osman realizes that we killed the judge?
Alaaddin will be dead by that time.
So it won't matter.
Be careful, though.
Nobody should know the judge is dead...
..until the trial is over.
The judge will be dead.
I don't know..
...if the devil
is needed while there is this woman.
No devils can be better than you, Ulcay.
You yourself killed
the child of the woman who you call devil.
There's always someone greater.
Let's go kill the judge.
This is the place where I last saw Gonca.
The way splits into two here.
-Gokmen.
-My Shahzade.
You go north
with the alps who are coming from behind.
Kanyumaz and I will go south.
Gokmen.
Nobody will go back to the
tribe before finding Alaaddin and Gonca.
As you order, my Shahzade.
Kill Alaaddin wherever you see him.
My Shahzade, what about Gonca Hatun?
My father is going to punish her personally.
-Come on!
-Alps, let's go!
Praise be to my talented Hatun.
My Alaeddin.
My rose
What happened?
Are you sick of me on day one?
Why do you look upset? Tell me.
I'm afraid about what's going to happen.
I always get you in trouble.
I always bring trouble.
Yes. You always cause trouble for me.
But it's a sweet trouble.
Come here.
Don’t you worry.
We promised each other.
Their evil intentions
and ambitions for the throne...
..cannot stop our love.
We will be the ones who will win.
If Allah permits, Alaeddin.
So? What will we eat?
I've prepared the food.
But these are the last ones from the hunt.
The boiler will be empty tomorrow, is that so?
Are you testing your man with hunger on day one?
Right.
If my man wanders around and picks daisies
he will drink
water instead of eating food tomorrow.
Okay then. I learned my lesson.
I'll go hunting tomorrow morning.
I will bring the best foods for my Hatun.
Well, we will see.
Put some so we can eat, come on.
My Scholar.
You're so smart.
But we will eat together with everyone.
Is that so?
Very well, let it be that way.
Talented Hatun.
Alaeddin.
Alaeddin, no.
-Gonca.
-Bala?
Bala.
-Bala.
-Osman.
You had a nightmare.
Calm down. Just calm down.
Ibrahim and Melike.
They were hanging
Alaeddin and Gonca.
I ran but I couldn't get there on time.
I couldn't get there, Osman.
They couldn't breathe.
They couldn't breathe, Osman.
Come here, come.
Who are you? Open your face.
-Boran Bey. -Brothers.
I have something to say to Osman Bey.
How dare you come here!
Turahan, brother!
Brother! Turahan! Stop
-Hold him!
-I said I have something to say to Osman Bey!
Hey!
Turahan! Stop, brother.
Let's listen to him.
Boran Bey, from now on
you shouldn't have anything to say to my Bey.
But if you want to die in the hands of my Bey...
...let's go there, then.
Thank you, Aykurt.
Come on.
This nightmare you just saw
is a good sign.
They both will walk a long way.
This is a sign of it.
And you can't get Alaeddin out of your mind.
That's why you're always dreaming about him.
Right. Right.
What are you doing? Are you working?
I worked, my Bala. When did you see me not working?
Every time I look
here, I see the way leading to Bursa.
While Alaeddin is a fugitive, Osman?
You mothers always
exaggerate everything.
Just wait.
I didn't leave them hungry when I was raising them,
We taught them lessons.
Don't you worry.
They had their lessons. They’ll take
care of it, don't worry.
Right, that's right.
What about the court?
Just wait.
First, take a look at this.
This is Mekece.
Its location is so crucial.
Because,
behind this there is Bursa, and then Iznik.
I'll move towards there.
We have many obstacles ahead of us.
Those among us, court first.
Alliance of Germiyans and Candars.
But if they make any tricks in the court
they will face our retaliation.
Harshly.
We will retaliate
and then I will take Alaeddin to his mother.
Right. They will return, if Allah permits.
What precautions do you think about the court?
Alaeddin thought about everything, he
prepared the Alps.
You will see it with your own eyes,
if Allah permits.
Tell me now.
Are we going to be able to see that...
...the Turkish banner will be put in Bursa?
I don't know if we can see it, my Osman,
you planted such a seed that
I have no doubt that the
whole world will see the Turkish banner.
I hope so..
-I hope so.
-So do I
May I come in, my Bey?
Come on in, Aykurt.
My Bey, Boran is here.
Let's leave after night prayer.
We need to get there...
...and determine the...
...proofs of court.
I have no doubt about you,
but everyone is talking
about this court, Qadi Rukneddin Effendi.
It will be a difficult case for us.
Let justice prevail.
After that, the apocalypse may come.
-What are you doing, dastard?
-Peace be upon you.
Rukneddin the judge.
Who are you?
Your death.
But not now.
Even your corpse is valuable.
We're leaving.
Dear judge.
My Bey.
Come.
Come here.
Sit down.
-My Bey.
-Sit down!
And you are also calling me your Bey, huh?
You let my captives run away.
You united with those against me.
You shouldn't have done this.
Since you came here...
...and risked death...
...you must have something to say.
I learned about the raid...
...at the graveyard...
...the last moment, my Bey...
I didn't have the chance...
I thought being among them...
...would be better than...
...watching from a distance.
Then you threw those arrows, huh?!
What was your goal?
To take the gold
from the palace...
Then you can
exile me, my Bey.
Allow me...
Let me fulfill my last duty.
Ibrahim Bey...
...wants to find Shahzade Alaeddin...
...and kill him.
I and Konur told him that...
...we knew the secret ways, my Bey.
We were going to tell Ibrahim Bey where you...
...were when you met Shahzade Alaeddin.
So Ibrahim Bey wants Alaeddin Bey.
We will tell him the way.
And that way..
...will bring Ibrahim to us.
You will wait for us at Asbahar.
Now leave.
Yes my Bey.
What about Olcay? Boran knows where he is.
Won't we kill him?
No.
Who is behind Olcay...
We will first learn that.
We will do it after that.
My Bey... Will you forgive Boran and Konur?
Their punishment was to be exiled from the tribe!
But they did not leave.
They did not leave.
Will I forgive them...
...or not?
Only Allah knows that.
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
Buldun mu Andra?
Have you found it Andra?
Buldum efendim, i§te Gonca’nin sa^lan.
Here, ma'am. Gonca's hair.
Gonca...
Revenge!
Death!
Death
Gonca..
Hatun
Gather everything and clean it up. Right now!
Melike Hatun
I was reciting Kuran for our son's soul, my Bey.
I haven't heard that you've arrived.
May Allah accept it, Hatun.
Your pain...
...increases day by day, I know.
But...
...let your heart find peace.
I will secure the justice.
Unless Kayis' hearts burn...
...my heart won't find peace.
And our son's soul will not find peace.
I want revenge as soon as possible.
I will wipe their names away...
...and teach everyone a lesson.
Walk! We are going!
Stop!
He will not die easily.
Speak!
Who are you? Who do you serve, huh?
Where did you take
Rukneddin the judge? What is your goal?
Look at me!
I can drown you here in your own blood!
Speak! Speak,
so I will take your poor life right away!
Where did you take Rukneddin the judge?
Tell me!
We were going to meet at Kuru Vadi
when we had it done.
Where exactly?
You will never be able to find it!
Come on!
How are we going to find them there?
This is looking for a needle in a haystack.
We have no other choice, Elcim.
They are trying to drag Alaeddin into a pit.
We will either take my brother out of there...
...or we will drown there together.
Holofira is coming this way.
She is also involved in the abduction
of Gonca Hatun.
She knows where she went.
We will take this Hatun. Come on.
Ambush.
We are not going to let
them go! We will take the Hatun! Come on!
I will never surrender to you!
You
You have nowhere to escape.
You will tell us where
Alaeddin Bey and Gonca Hatun are.
I don't know. I don't know. Let me go.
Holofira Hatun..
We know that you abducted Gonca together.
You will tell us how you killed Shahzade Ahmed.
You will tell us where that murderer
Alaeddin is hiding.
Enough!
Alaeddin is not a murderer!
But if you don't tell me where they are, I won't
care that you are a Hatun, I will kill you.
Alright. I'll tell you.
They are in Kiyidibi.
What if you are lying?
I am not lying.
But you are making a big mistake.
Alaeddin is not a murderer.
I am his witness, he is not a killer.
When we were leaving the marketplace...
...Ahmed was alive.
Who killed him then? Do you also know that?
Who was it if it was not Alaeddin Bey?
I don't know!
I will tell what she said to my Bey.
You take her to the Frontier Marketplace safely.
-Come on.
-Husrev.
You go with Tugay.
Osman Bey's spies are around.
Alright. You are right.
There are footprints here.
My Shahzade.
Ulcay's whip.
It seems they clashed here.
Is there a cave nearby, Kanyumaz?
There are many caves
towards Dokuz Kaya la r, my Shahzade.
Right so. They are hiding in one of the caves.
We will check each hole, Kanyumaz.
As you command, my Shahzade.
Come on then.
Let us see your skills, Alaeddin Bey.
You will see.
I will bring you
the most delicious catch you ever saw.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Alright. I will wait for you then.
Alright. You wait.
My Shahzade.
-I could've also gone.
-No.
I will bring the catch today.
You protect my Hatun.
Hasan. Baysungur.
Stay cautious.
Come on.
The men will arrive to the valley soon.
We need to hurry.
You will be sent to hell soon as well.
Rukneddin the judge.
Hell is a place for devils like you.
That is the place you will go in the end.
Where will we start from?
There are many trees. We do not have good vision.
This valley goes to Karlidaglar.
We know they are around here somewhere.
Even that gives me hope.
With Allah's permission we will find them.
There are a lot off trees around.
It will be hard for them to move with horses.
However, it is good for moving without being seen.
Whatever they want to do with the judge...
..they are onto something secret.
However, we will find out.
We will find out and make them pay.
We will reach north first.
Thank you, Holofira.
You did your duty.
You were more brave
than those we called brothers once.
After what you have done for me..
..it was nothing, Osman Bey.
However, you going to
Frontier Marketplace does not feel right.
They can not touch me, you know that.
They do not want to be bad with Emperor.
Holofira is entrusted to us, my Bey. Do not worry.
Osman Bey.
Even if you do not see me as your comrade..
..I never left your cause.
That is why I took those gold.
I drew the location where the gold is here.
Let the alps go and take it.
You think this is about gold.
Still.
You went against tradition.
You went against our command.
You fell into arrogance and spilled each
other's blood.
There is no way for me to forgive you.
However, I see that..
..you do not forgive yourself neither.
If you do not forgive us..
..we never will, my Bey.
If Allah permits,
we become martyrs for this cause..
..and our Creator forgives us.
Allow us to stay among
them until this trouble goes away, my Bey.
Holofira. May you arrive safely.
Bring the alps.
My Bey.
The news are correct Osman has sent
someone to send word to Alaeddin.
Who?
the Byzantine noblewoman called Holofira.
She was there when Ahmed Bey was murdered.
If we can make her talk before the trial..
..it will be good for us.
Well thought, Tugay.
Where is the girl now?
Now, Boran and Konur are bringing her here.
Where is Alaeddin?
Alaeddin is in the cave at Kayadibi, my Bey.
First, I will kill Osman's son myself.
Then I will kill his people..
..for protecting him.
-Then, you know the rest, Tugay.
-I do, my Bey.
The rest is the field of battle.
Take alps from me as well.
Do not go with so few, Ibrahim Bey.
I've got enough to break Osman's cub.
Thank you.
Come on!
Traitors!
Gonca Hatun, run!
Hasan, take Gonca Hatun and leave!
I will stall them!
Do not run away! You have to pay!
Mehmed Bey, stay back.
-Get out of the way, Baysungur.
-Stay back, Mehmed Bey.
Gonca!
-Gonca! Do not run! Come here!
-Run!
Gonca!
Mehmed Bey!
You are making a mistake! Gonca Hatun run faster!
Brothers.
-Hasan!
-Run, Gonca Hatun!
Run! Save your life!
Gonca
What did you do Gonca? What did you do!
You stained our honor!
From now on, you will be locked up!
You can not do anything!
I am married to Alaeddin now!
Gonca!
-What have you done, Gonca? -Get off!
You heard me.
I'm his wife now
I've always lived with my honor.
Besides, speaking of honor,
...why do you think of women only?
Were you honorable while
working with Candar and doing things...
...behind Osman Bey's back?
-Where is Alaaddin? Where? -Get off!
He's gone to the tribe.
He's going to see Osman Bey.
If you care about me even a little,
...leave us alone.
-Don't mess with us.
-No.
You won't find peace anymore, Gonca.
If Alaaddin is a true man
...he'll come and surrender.
Then I'll kill him even before the trial.
And there will be no marriage behind.
Do you have no mercy?
-Do you have no mercy left at all?
-Shut up!
We're going back to the frontier market.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Shahzade.
Take Gonca to the horses.
We're leaving shortly.
As you order, my Shahzade.
Don't touch me.
Come on!
Lay an ambush near the cave.
When Alaaddin comes, kill him.
As you order, my Shahzade.
If Alaaddin survives, he'll come after Gonca.
Then I'll kill him personally.
As they say,
...justice is putting everything where it belongs.
So you're being
put in the grave before you die, Judge.
You can’t overcome justice by vile actions.
It's more important than the life.
The fake judge taking
your place will overcome the justice.
Even you'd be surprised to see that.
But you're going to die.
Allah's justice...
His justice is everlasting.
He will overcome you.
Before Ahmed's body rots,
...Alaaddin's head will fall.
Then nothing
will be able to stop the war of beylics.
Who attacked the inn
and looked for the judge, Ulcay Khan?
No news from them.
It doesn't matter.
Judge Rukneddin is dead.
It doesn't matter even if they all die.
Before Judge Rukneddin's dead body is found,
...the people after us can do nothing to us.
Calm down. Jackal. Calm down.
Come on
My magic is working.
Look there.
They're all going to be in my hands gradually.
Yakup Bey.
We brought Alaaddin's
accomplice who abducted your daughter.
Osman was taking this hatun to
Constantinople to stop her from testifying.
Alright, Beys.
You proved to be on the side of justice.
You will be rewarded.
Killers.
You all will get your shares from my wrath.
All of you.
Andra.
-You snake!
-You are the snake!
You helped Alaaddin while he was killing
my son, huh?
Ha?
Your son was
alive while leaving the frontier market.
Someone else killed him.
You're lying! Lying!
Melike Hatun!
This is not a time when we should act with anger.
Stop now.
She's a Byzantine princess.
When the time comes
...she will serve us.
Fine.
So be it.
If she's to testify,
...I'm putting my sword down.
-But..
If she tells lies
...we will put the rope around her neck.
Don't be worrying, Melike Hatun.
Thank You, my Allah!
Our stomachs are going to be filled today.
Guice?
-What’s the matter?
-Alaaddin Bey.
-Mehmed Bey came here.
-And?
He took Gonca Hatun away.
What are you saying?
Alps laid an ambush near the cave to kill you.
Where have they taken my Gonca?
To the frontier market.
What now, Alaaddin Bey?
I know what to do.
I won't leave my hatun to them.
I won't!
Don't do this, Alaaddin Bey!
They won’t let you live.
Only Allah can know that!
Come on!
Alaaddin!
Alaaddin, come out!
Come out, my son's killer!
There are no killers here.
No killers in my family either.
But don't push us too much.
Don't harm the alps!
But the blood of Ulcay's dogs...
...is halal to you!
This is the fight of
justice! Attack, warriors! Show no mercy!
Come here, Ulcay's dogs!
Allah is Eternal!
I'm not lying. Alaaddin Bey didn't kill anyone.
Gonca and he loved each other.
So they ran away. That's all.
Holofira Hatun.
Don’t go too far.
Do not.
Don't you
attempt to defend those killers against me.
Take her..
...to the cage tent!
I know how to make you speak.
Come on!
You surprised me, Beys.
You turned out to have noble blood.
You're on the side of the right.
From now on, I want to see you two on my side.
You should know that.
While Osman's children are as arrogant as him,
...doing the otherwise wouldn't suit us, Yakup Bey.
We always avoid the arrogance, Yakup Bey.
It's an honor for us to be on your side.
Alright then. Be my guests.
But you will never get smarter.
You first let the Shahzade beat you, then me.
But... getting hurt is your fate.
Sure... If you are going to stand against us.
You were not able to crush me, but I
will crush you all under my feet Cerkutay.
Enough! Enough, Ibrahim Bey!
Drop your sword.
Do you want my life...
...after taking my son's life?
Take it then.
But..
Your debt to Candar is increasing, know that.
My intention was never...
...to take your life.
If'it were, I would have done it a thousand times.
I told you to wait until the trial.
Is that so?
You captured us, Osman Bey!
What would have changed if I hadn't?
You're gathering your people and army...
...and getting ready for war. Don't I know that?
I am a father! I lost my son!
Ibrahim Bey!
Enough now.
Stop hiding behind your son's pain.
It doesn't suit you.
I will be a curse to you...
...and your so-called state...
...which is just a tribe looking like village!
Ibrahim Bey.
You destroyed the Cobanogullari...
...with the help of Ilkhanate...
...and now you sit on the Beylic chair.
We don't wear leashes around our necks.
We will not bow to you...
...or Olcaytu.
Know your place, Osman Bey!
What kind of accusation is that?
-You should know your place!
I know why you came here.
You came to bring trouble to my lands.
You even planned
that wedding for your evil alliance.
Right!
Admit it!
You ruined our wedding you killed my son!
No, no, Ibrahim Bey!
I arranged Alaeddin and
Gonca's marriage to prevent the wedding.
They are married now. But know this.
We didn't kill your son.
Now make your decision.
Will you come with us to court...
...or will you die here?
You can't stop the bloodshed, Osman Bey.
Your game was...
...ruined by the blood of my Ahmed.
Don't you do that! Enough!
The innocence of Alaeddin will be revealed.
And you will leave my lands.
Drop your sword!
Drop it!
Yes.
Alps!
Take Ibrahim Bey and his Alps...
...the way they deserve.
Birds will feed on...
...the others' bodies.
-Yes my Bey.
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
My son's blood was shed on these dowries.
Gonca..
Gonca...
I will burn you and...
...your lover just like these dowries!
You will beg to me to die!
Walk!
Come on!
The day is today.
My son... The one who caused this has arrived.
The one who shed your blood will also come.
He will come.
Apparently my son made his move before Ibrahim Bey.
He will come soon.
You've come back...
...to your home again.
Did you think you could escape from me?
This isn't my home.
She is not even embarrassed!
You snake...
You caused the death of my son!
Know your place, Melike Hatun!
Who are you to touch me, huh?
I'll cut that snake tongue of yours, Gonca.
You did not obey me.
You embarrassed me.
You united with
that murderer Alaeddin and ran away.
How can you still say those things?
Alaeddin is not a killer!
He didn't kill Ahmed!
You're still lying.
But I know how to make you talk.
Your honour... -Don't you dare!
Don’t!
You don’t have the right to insult my honor, Hatun!
You're the one who asked for the hand of a girl...
...who loved someone
else without asking or seeking permission!
We'll see.
I haven't committed
any dishonorable act, thanks to Allah.
I left and..
...married the man I loved!
What did you do?
How could you disobey me?
You..
You ruined me, Gonca.
Now...
...I don't have a daughter like you.
Traitor.
I did not betray anyone.
Hit me! Go on! Hit me! -Gonca! -Don't! Hit me!
You cannot hurt me!
You said..
...you did not have a daughter like me...
Now I don’t have a father like you!
Don't, father!
Take her to the caged tent.
The judge will decide what will happen to her.
My child's blood is in Alaeddin's hands, Osman.
Even if you don't believe it, he's a murderer.
But by protecting him, you ruin your afterlife.
Ibrahim Bey, this is the bridge of As-Sirat.
Do not try to kill my
child, the consequences will be heavy.
Look.
Alaeddin is innocent.
You'll see it one day.
After all, the murderer is clear for me.
When the court is set up and the verdict is given
I'll punish him with my own hands.
-Osman Bey.
-I hope nothing's bad.
Guice Hatun. She's Gonca Hatun's friend, my Bey.
Osman Bey. Mehmed Bey kidnapped Gonca Hatun.
So, Alaeddin?
How's Alaeddin?
They kidnapped Gonca
Hatun while Alaeddin Bey was not there.
They went after him too, but he got rid of them.
He went after them, to the Frontier Marketplace.
Thankfully.
Now the justice will be done.
Soon he will be captured.
That's enough! That's enough!
I kept quiet until now.
But if my child gets hurt...
...then my wrath will be heavy, Ibrahim Bey.
Keep that in mind.
Take Ibrahim Bey to the tribe.
Yes, my Bey. Come on.
What are we going to do now, my Bey?
Alaeddin might do anything to take Gonca.
We will not jackals get him. Come on, move.
Please don't do any
madness and come after me, Alaeddin.
Please don't.
He’s not brave enough to surrender.
But I thought you were brave.
How could you do this to usz Gonca?
If you were as brave enough as Alaeddin,
you'd have stood behind me and be my brother.
You betrayed us!
-How can you still talk?
-I didn't betray you.
I loved him.
I just loved him.
But what do you know about love?
I saw it.
I saw it
when I looked at Alaeddin
Orhan Bey and Fatma.
You've never loved me, Mehmed Bey.
You've never loved your household, Gonca.
-You embarrassed us.
-I loved you.
I loved you more than anything else.
But what did y'all do?
What did you do?
First you crushed me.
Was it enough? It was not!
Then you broke me.
But that was not enough for you!
You tore me apart!
I loved you, sister.
I protected you from even the wind.
Just so you don't risk yourself for someone else.
I kept you away
from Alaeddin just because I love you.
But it's all in vain.
Love blinded you.
You can’t see the truth.
Gunduz Bey.
Where is Osman Bey? What's going on?
Gonca Hatun and alps were caught.
What are you saying, Gunduz Bey?
-What about Alaeddin? -He went after them.
Osman Bey went after him.
He's afraid that he will surrender.
-Mother, my brother won't stay there.
-My Allah, protect them.
He will not let Gonca alone with them.
He will surrender.
Bala Hatun!
You will not be able to spoil justice!
My son's death will be avenged.
Sooner or later your child will die.
While we have you
they cannot hurt my child or my daughter-in-law.
You will be treated
as they are treated, Ibrahim Bey.
Very well.
So you are ignoring the
vile and dastard action
your child did.
You're protecting him!
Both your heart
and justice are rotten.
Enough! Know your place, Ibrahim Bey!
My child is innocent.
And we will always protect our children.
Don't make any mistake and say a word.
-Take him.
-Come on.
Bala Hatun! You will pay for this!
We will see who will pay, Ibrahim Bey!
We will see.
Mother. Should we go
to the Frontier Marketplace for my brother?
Wait, daughter. Let's wait for your father first.
I’m here, my Gonca.
I'll not leave you alone.
Murderer!
How dare you kidnap my sister?
You ruined him, you ruined my sister!
Alaeddin, what have you done?
Come on!
Open the way.
Open the way!
My Allah, please protect Alaeddin.
-Who will save you from me now?
-Don't you dare!
Don't you dare!
Don’t you dare make any move!
Are you going to take the life of another child?
Yakup Bey.
-If Alaeddin gets hurt.
-He will!
He will get hurt.
He will die as my son did.
Then...
..your Bey, Ibrahim Bey..
..he will die too.
Think about it well.
Your son...
...comes and gives in to our justice.
You are holding Ibrahim Bey for nothing.
The wisest of ulemas..
..Rukneddin the judge is coming.
First, everyone drop your weapons.
If justice was found with sword..
..we would've wear it ourselves.
And if you wanted to solve your issue with swords..
..then why did you call me for?
Welcome, dear judge.
Drop them!
Do you want a trial..
..or should we deal here.
If I were to deal with you..
..I would've had your head at the tribe.
Tell us, dear judge.
No one will touch anyone until the trial.
Will you do the trial here?
This here is not fit for the trial.
A lot of blood can be spilled here.
I will decide the location.
I will let you know tomorrow.
You will enter the trial without swords.
Justice will be done.
Dear judge is right!
Alright, dear judge.
I will get him back just as I delivered him.
Otherwise, if something happens..
..you can not pay for it.
Tomorrow, everything will be decided..
..at the trial.
Osman Bey.
-Son.
-My Bey.
I trust you, father.
Your innocence will be revealed.
I will come back to get you.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
Father.
Take good care of this.
Do not worry.
I will keep it safe.
-Cerkutay!
-My Bey!
Come on.
Take him!
Sun will go down soon.
There is no trace of the judge.
They must've been at north.
Where are they?
Where did they take the judge?
Who are these men, Orhan? What will we do now?
I do not know, Elcim Hatun.
Only thing I know..
..is that my brother's life, Alaeddin's
life is in danger.
We will not know about their
intentions, unless we find Rukneddin the judge.
We will check each tree if needed!
We will find them, come on.
Elcim Hatun!
This is the same bead ball as the one at the inn.
Rukneddin the judge.
Has left trace for us.
It seems he wants us to find him.
Come on. We will look for tracks.
There, found you.
This way! Come on, to horses!
Where are they.
They must've gone anywhere.
What is that?
The soil is freshly dug
They stepped on it with horses.
Come on, in the name of Allah.
Allah.
My Allah, protect us.
Rukneddin the judge.
This is our..
..paper we sent for the trial.
Look here.
It has his signature here.
He even tried to do bring justice while dying.
Scoundrels.
They killed him like cowards!
They played tricks like cowards!
Someone..
..someone does not want this trial to happen.
Someone does not want this trial.
Or, the other way.
Someone..
..wants to see this trial with their own judge.
Alaeddin.
-To the horses, come on!
-Orhan!
-We have a day's road, how will we catch up?
-We will.
We will catch up no matter what, Elcim Hatun.
My brother's life..
..my Alaeddin's life is in my hands.
Osman.
Where is Alaeddin?
Alaeddin surrendered.
There will be a trial tomorrow.
He is at Frontier Marketplace for now.
The trial..
..will be at the place..
..where the judge will decide, they said.
Do not worry.
Father.
They will not let my brother in peace there.
They can not do anything.
We have Ibrahim Bey.
Your brother's innocence will be proven.
Do not worry, my dear daughter.
They have been blinded.
They will not want to see the truth.
I fear that they will try to do traitorous acts.
What if the judge does not provide justice?
What if he decides..
..may Allah prevent it, father.
Do not worry.
We do not doubt the judge's justice.
However..
..Yakup Bey and Melike Hatun..
..will surely cause trouble.
And we will do our move accordingly.
If the judge is here. So where is Orhan?
I hope he isn't in trouble. May Allah forbid that.
Well... That's what bothers me.
Now news from Orhan. I've sent alps after him.
I hope they won't attempt to harm him.
I hope they won't try to deceive
us in the trial...
...and put rope around my son's neck!
If they do, I'll
burn down the court over their heads!
You said there would be no weapons. How?
Aykurt! Turahan!
We have no swords, but...
...we have secret weapons...
...my Alaaddin Ali prepared.
Now...
Finish your preparations.
Be ready to fight.
As you order, my Bey.
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
Swords...
...will be hidden like this.
They will be put under
Germiyanoglu and Candaroglu like this.
I'll give these
to one of those on duty in the court.
And he'll place them in our section.
If a problem comes up
...we won’t be without weapons there.
A problem will come up, Mehmed Bey.
It will.
We'll turn the place into a bloodbath.
My son died.
Nothing but blood will cool off my heart.
Osman won't go there unprepared either.
For this reason, our alps
will wait somewhere close to the court.
And we'll be all prepared.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Don't be angry with me, Gonca.
I shouldn't be?
Why did you surrender, Alaaddin?
Don't you know what is going to happen?
What did I tell you, my hatun?
What?
I will never leave you alone.
I promised you.
I can't break my promise.
My Alaaddin, what if the judge doesn't believe us?
What will we do then?
We know the truth, Gonca.
I didn't kill Ahmed.
I don't know..
...if you killed him or not, but...
I'll kill you, Alaaddin.
-Brother, stop! Don't do this!
-Well...
That would suit you, Mehmed.
You tied me up. Come.
This is how you can only kill me.
You are a dead man, Alaaddin.
I don't hear you.
Brother, stop! Stop
-Get off!
-Brother, please stop!
That's enough!
Please stop! Enough!
Not enough!
Not enough.
You disrespected us.
-Our honor...
-Shut up! We didn't do anything.
I tried to talk to you many times.
But you never listened, Mehmed.
I said I loved your sister.
I said I fell in love.
And you? What did you do?
I believe..
...neither you nor your love, Alaaddin.
You did this to prevent our alliance with Candar.
You can’t protect mysister.
Brother, stop! For Allah's sake! Please stop!
You took my sister from me.
My sister no longer trusts me.
You've left me without a sister, Alaaddin.
You did this, Mehmed.
You should have acted like a brother...
...and supported us.
Brother, please stop! Don't do this! Don't!
Please, don't! Please stop!
You aren't a man who deserves to be supported!
You have to divorce my sister, Alaaddin!
You have to divorce my sister before you die!
Brother, please stop Please stop! Please!
Please! Leave him!
Please stop!
I'm not like you, Mehmed.
I'd do anything for my love.
I'd rather die than break my promise.
Please stop! You are mad! Please!
Brother, please stop!
Don't do this! Stop! You are mad! Stop!
-That's enough! Brother, please stop!
-Mehmed!
-Brother, stop! Stop!
-Leave him!
I won’t stop, father! I'm going to kill him!
I said stop.
They got Ibrahim Bey.
If this man dies
...Osman won't let him live.
You should be patient.
They're going to...
...be punished tomorrow, anyway.
Come on. Get out.
Alaaddin, are you alright?
I'm fine, Gonca.
I'm fine, my love.
I'm used to Mehmed's fists.
-Does it hurt?
-No, my love. It doesn't.
Alps! Sisters!
Today, we will
establish a court for Shahzade Alaeddin.
We will always stand by justice.
But... if we have to fight...
...at the end of the trial...
...we will fight.
Therefore, all of you will be ready.
When we give you the sign..
...your secret weapons will be revealed.
Come on!
Osman Bey said it... He
said "brothers' blood should not be shed"
But they are framing Tall Shahzade.
Why would Muslims
do this to each other to shed blood?
Because they fall for the shaytaan's games.
He has such treacherous traps that...
...nafs makes you companions with shaytaan.
What are those traps?
You are the Sultan of words. You will
tell me, right?
Cowardice...
...considering yourself superior...
...the desire for power, fame, and glory...
...greed, sacrificing everything...
...for gold...
...serving the servants for properties...
Shaytaan has other traps, but...
...there is one trap...
...that is arrogance.
The love of self.
Thinking you deserve everything.
The Muslim who falls into that trap...
...walks with arrogance.
He slanders his brother...
...sheds his blood...
..and thinks he is right.
Like Cain.
Do you know Cain and Abel?
I do...
...but we are not Cain, right?
Not my Osman Bey. But are they Cain?
The slanderers?
We don't know who is Cain and who is Abel for sure.
But what we know is that...
...Osman Bey seeks peace to...
...avoid shedding brotherly blood.
He does not leave the true path...
...he does not fall into the traps of shaytaan.
Therefore...
...if there is anyone
to spread Islam's da'wah to the world...
...it is surely him.
Osman Bey...
Ibrahim Bey.
Today, justice will be established.
You speak of justice to a man...
...you unjustly took as a captive.
I don't believe a word you say, Osman Bey!
Is that so?
Will you not be
persuaded even by what the judge says?
Ha?
Despite him...
Will you still try to kill my son?
If your son...
...had not made a move, none of this
would have happened.
Ibrahim Bey is poisoned with hatred.
He blames others...
...he never blames himself.
But...
...those like him...
...only hurt themselves.
Release his hands.
There's no need to tie his hands.
Come on. Take him.
O people...
The court that will happen today
might turn into a battlefield anytime!
Everyone will be ready!
Everyone will be ready for a battle!
Come on!
My Shahzade...
Holofira... Are you alright?
Come on! Put him in the cart!
These are your last breaths.
Take a deep one.
Melike Hatun.
We must not delay justice.
Let the truth be exposed.
Those involved will be punished.
It is time.
Your poor fear won’t delay your death.
Don't you trust the great
justice? Why did you gather here like mice?
We trust justice...
...but we do not trust your dastardness!
If you do not trust great justice...
...just as we got under the soil before death...
...we know how to rain from the holy sky.
I will bring the sky down upon you Olcay!
I stand before you with an army that loves death...
...as much as you love life!
Now get lost or I'll crush you!
You escaped from me once.
But there won't be a second time, Gunduz.
The skies above will also determine your fate.
He is still talking, get lost!
Is everything ready, Yakup Bey?
We are sitting on our swords.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Sit down.
On the 10th day of Shawwal...
...the trial for the accusation of Osman
Bey's son Alaeddin...
...murdering the son of Ibrahim Bey...
...from the Candar tribe, Ahmed Bey...
...has begun.
On the day Ahmed Bey was killed...
...you were in that tent to abduct Gonca Hatun...
...right, Alaeddin Bey?
Yes, dear judge
-But I did not kill..
-Do not answer...
...before you are asked to speak, Alaeddin Bey.
Did Ahmed Bey resist you...
...or a fight happen between you?
Yes, dear judge
And you are still claiming that you did
not kill Ahmed Bey.
Do you know where you stabbed the dagger?
It was Ahmed Bey who drew his dagger.
I did not touch my dagger.
Could you... fight my
son when he was holding a dagger?
He is lying, dear judge.
Ibrahim Bey,
do not speak before I ask you to speak.
I was not alone there, dear judge.
Dear judge... We want you to hear the witnesses.
Gonca... and Holofira.
They were there.
Gonca Hatun.
Holofira Hatun. Come forward.
Are they going to be your witnesses, Osman Bey?
One of them is the
Hatun of the accused Alaeddin Bey...
...the other is
a Christian who is living with your people.
Besides, both are women!
Their testimonies are invalid.
It is not enough!
These two Hatuns are also the accomplices.
If the guilt is proven,
they will be sentenced like Alaeddin Bey.
Dear judge.. What are you saying?
You're saying our witnesses'...
...testimonies are invalid for our innocence...
...and that our evidence is insufficient.
Then tell me
Show me the
evidence that proves Alaeddin killed Ahmed!
We'll be there soon, come on!
Just to blame us...
You're doing this so that we turn
against each other when Alaeddin is out.
Now tell me.
Show me the proof
that Ahmed was not killed by someone else.
While there are many suspects
you're talking about a murderer that doesn't exist.
You're diverting the court from its purpose.
This is not the place to talk about theories,
but it is the place to talk about truth.
What if our theory is more true than your verdict?
Then...
...you will show the
proof that Alaeddin killed Ahmed Bey.
We are the servants of justice, we exist for this.
When the proof is not enough
we make the verdict.
If everything was clear, we wouldn't be needed.
Before I tell my verdict, I'd like to hear
last defense of Alaeddin Bey.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
"Then they are all returned to Allah
their True Master.
Judgment is His.
And He is the...
...Swiftest Reckoner."
[Surah Al-An'am - 62]
You are distorting The Creator's justice.
Show a precedent for such a verdict.
Your punishment will be heavy,
dear judge.
But don't worry.
My Creator is the Swiftest Reckoner.
-Don't you forget.
-All the signs lead to you, Alaeddin Bey.
Isn't Gonca your Hatun?
Wasn't Ahmed Bey your rival?
You were the first one to question...
...even if you weren't there.
Such a verdict was inevitable.
Since everything is clear, it is time for verdict.
First of all, I will give
the verdict of the so-called witnesses.
Holofira Hatun.
She will be banished and she will not
come to the lands of any of the Beyliks.
Gonca Hatun will be spared.
She will be given back to her household.
-And the marriage will be over.
-What are you talking about, dear judge?
This is not justice, this is not the right verdict!
You even captured us
saying that the court will be set up.
And now, are you going to go against the
The judge's verdict?
May Allah protect us
from shedding the blood of our brothers.
Gunduz Bey!
Infidels want this from us.
But we will never give them what they want.
Thank Allah.
Right.
Right, but let's be prepared.
Tell us your verdict, dear judge.
Alaeddin Bey...
...was found guilty of
the murder of Candaroglu Ahmed Bey.
Thankfully.
There's life in retaliation.
That is why, Alaeddin Bey will be executed.
No, son. Alaeddin, no.
Dear judge.
When you don't have any proof
how can you convict the innocent?
Osman, Osman.
They are going to hang our son.
-Alaeddin!
-Gonca!
-Mehmed!
-Let go off me. Alaeddin!
Let go off me! Alaeddin!
Let go off me! Let go off me!
Let me go! Alaeddin!
Alaeddin! Osman Bey!
Alaeddin! I said let him go!
Alaeddin! No! No!
Let him go!
Let go off him! Alaeddin! Alaeddin!
No! No! Alaeddin! Let him go!
Stop!
Brother.
This judge is fake!
They killed the true judge, Rukneddin.
Would you do this to distort justice, Osman Bey?
Shut up!
So you're here with your swords?
Show the letter that Osman Bey invited you.
-You are setting me up!
-They are lying!
They are lying to save their murderer son!
Is that so?
Look at me.
This is the plan of Kayis!
Is this your justice? Move away!
Is this your justice?
Justice?
Justice.
Is this your justice?
Is it?
You'd kill my son with a fake judge, is that so?
You came with
your swords to kill us all, is that so?
Is that so?
There's no such thing, Osman Bey!
We didn't know that judge was fake.
What about you?
You hid sword inside of the banner.
No matter how many traps the hunter sets,
the wolf finds a way.
You were going to kill us.
You were going to kill my son.
Do you think I'd just watch?
Justice doesn't hurt, you're wrong!
Shut up! Shut up!
You're still talking.
Ibrahim Bey. Ibrahim Bey.
They are killing the judge in front of us.
Do something.
How have we survived this long?
With justice.
By ruling with justice.
But if injustice gets inside,
then peace will be gone in the nation.
I will not let anyone use justice for revenge.
I will not let anyone use justice for their
evil purposes!
How dare you talk like this?
Are you the State?
Everywhere I set foot
I'm the Bey, and I'm the State.
Come here.
As long as there are dastards like him,
as long as there are
those who make plans behind our back
from now
from now on,
I'm the justice.
Visit turkision.com for more!